<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<CorbisCorp>
	<team>
		<Headline>LEADERSHIP</Headline>
		<Intro>
			The individuals charged with managing Corbis contribute diverse skills to the common goal of maintaining the company's position as the industry leader.
		</Intro>
		<teamName>Executive Management</teamName>
		<Leader>
			<ID>1</ID>
			<Name>Gary Shenk</Name>
			<Title>CEO</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/gary_shenk.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_gary_shenk.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					As CEO, Gary Shenk has overall responsibility for the business strategy and leadership in accelerating Corbis’ position as an innovative Internet media company and leading creative resource for advertising, marketing and media professionals worldwide.
				</p>
				<p>
					As part of a planned leadership succession, Shenk was appointed President of Corbis in November, 2006, overseeing all of Corbis’ integrated market facing functions including sales, marketing, image licensing and Rights Services.
				</p>
				<p>
					Prior to his promotion to the role of President, Shenk was Senior Vice President of Images, where he spearheaded a transformation of the image licensing business from an editorial focus to a complete offering with world-class historical, editorial, entertainment and creative photography. Shenk joined Corbis in 2003 to lead the company’s newly established Rights Services unit, and he executed a series of acquisitions and business development successes that helped to position the company as the world leader in this field.
				</p>
				<p>
					Prior to joining Corbis, Shenk was a founder and general manager of one of Hollywood’s leading media licensing agencies, FlixMix, a wholly owned subsidiary of Universal Studios, where he was instrumental in establishing new licensing formats and brokering deals between studios, talent agencies, and music companies. Shenk began his relationship with Universal while he was a leader in the media and entertainment practice of The Boston Consulting Group.
				</p>
				<p>
					Shenk is a graduate of Harvard College and the Wharton Business School. Prior to his graduate studies he lived and worked in Moscow where he met his wife, Ioulia.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>2</ID>
			<Name>Mark Sherman</Name>
			<Title>SVP, GreenLight</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Mark_Sherman.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_Mark_Sherman.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Mark Sherman is SVP and head of GreenLight, a Corbis company that is one of the world’s leading intellectual property services firms.  Sherman is a member of the Executive Team and is based in Seattle.
				</p>
				<p>
					As SVP of GreenLight, Sherman oversees a global business across three continents. His team conducts thousands of clearances of iconic media every year on behalf of clients such as Hallmark’s ‘Say It With Sound’ cards, ScreenLife’s Scene It?® games and leading advertising agencies around the world. He also oversees GreenLights’ Rights Representation group, which represents the estates of iconic personalities including Albert Einstein, the Wright Brothers and Steve McQueen.
				</p>
				<p>
					Prior to joining GreenLight, Sherman was director of account management at fine.com, a business solutions provider.  Previously, he spent seven years at the Walt Disney Studios in Los Angeles, where he was an Associate Producer and served as director of creative development and production. He started his professional career at Touche Ross, now Deloitte and Touche, and also worked in New York for several years in independent film production.
				</p>
				<p>
					Sherman is an active member in the local Seattle community and sits on the board of Solid Ground Washington and the Seattle Children’s Theater. He received his B.A. from Stanford University and his M.B.A. from Dartmouth's Tuck School of Business.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>3</ID>
			<Name>Ivan Purdie</Name>
			<Title>SVP, Sales &amp; Service</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Ivan_Purdie.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_Ivan_Purdie.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					As SVP of Sales &amp; Service and a member of the Executive Team, Ivan Purdie is responsible for all sales teams and activities worldwide. After joining Corbis in January 2005, he served first as sales director in the U.K. and then as director of Corbis’ sales operations in EMEA, a region that saw a significant growth in sales under his leadership.  Purdie is currently based in London.
				</p>
				<p>
					Purdie has nearly twenty years of experience within the advertising, marketing and media sectors, specializing in sales and business development. Prior to joining Corbis, Purdie was Executive Vice President at Medialink, managing a global marketing services business for the advertising, corporate marketing and public relations industries.
				</p>
				<p>
					Previously, he was Sales Director for Image Bank, a leading stock photography company later acquired by Getty Images. While at Image Bank, he oversaw the launch of the company’s first online sales model. Purdie began his career with the one of Europe’s most influential media and publishing companies, Emap.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>4</ID>
			<Name>Jim Mitchell</Name>
			<Title>
				SVP, Corporate Development &amp; General Counsel
			</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Jim_Mitchell.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_Jim_Mitchell.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Jim Mitchell, SVP &amp; General Counsel, is responsible for Corbis’ legal and business development activities. As a member of the Executive Team, he establishes Corbis’ vision in the area of intellectual property rights as it leads the industry in finding new and effective ways to protect and manage these rights. In this role, he oversees the company’s in-house legal team and all of Corbis' legal matters, including risk management, corporate transactions, intellectual property rights, licensing agreements, and source and representative relationships.   Mitchell is based in Seattle.
				</p>
				<p>
					Prior to joining Corbis in 2000, Mitchell was a partner at the law firm of Cozen O'Connor, focusing on insurance coverage, insurance defense and commercial litigation. From 1993 to 1999, he was an associate at Lane Powell Spears Lubersky, also focusing on insurance coverage, insurance defense and commercial litigation.
				</p>
				<p>
					Mitchell received his J.D. from the University of Puget Sound School of Law in 1992 and his B.B.A. from Southern Methodist University in 1988.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>5</ID>
			<Name>Barry Allen</Name>
			<Title>CFO</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Barry_Allen.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_Barry_Allen.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Barry Allen, CFO, oversees the financial management for Corbis. He joined the company in 2008 to manage Corbis' financial operations and accelerate its continued growth. Allen is a member of the company’s Executive Team and is based in Seattle.
				</p>
				<p>
					Allen has more than 25 years of global experience in diverse senior executive leadership roles at public and private companies in the Internet, enterprise technology and real estate sectors. He is a recognized expert in global mergers and acquisitions, responsible for the acquisition or sale of more than a dozen companies, as well as helping to grow revenues in dynamic environments.
				</p>
				<p>
					Allen joins Corbis from Housevalues, a leading provider of marketing and technology services to real estate professionals, where as CFO he was responsible for diversifying the company's revenue stream and product offerings while solidifying the company’s core business. Previously, Allen was CFO of Move.com where he helped the company significantly increase market share and revenue growth before negotiating its sale, one of the largest for an Internet company at the time. Prior to Move.com, he served as CFO and then president and chief operating officer of Marketwave, a provider of enterprise-class e-business intelligence software.
				</p>
				<p>
					Barry began his career at Coopers &amp; Lybrand, an international CPA firm, after receiving his BA in Business Administration from the University of Washington.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>6</ID>
			<Name>Nairn Nerland</Name>
			<Title>SVP, Networks</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Nairn_Nerland.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/sm_Nairn_Nerland.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Nairn Nerland, SVP, Networks, is a member of the Executive Team with responsibility for all Web and marketing activities for the company’s images brands including Corbis, Veer and SnapVillage. Nerland is based in Calgary.
				</p>
				<p>
					Nerland brings 20 years of business experience in mergers and acquisitions, as well as in international publicly traded companies in both Canada and the United States. Nerland has held senior executive positions at several successful technology companies in Calgary.
				</p>
				<p>
					As CFO of four high-tech companies – RenoWorks Software Inc., EyeWire Inc., Harbor Systems Management Ltd. and Zi Corporation – Nerland was in charge of financial planning, public reporting, tax planning, financing, and assisting the CEOs in strategic direction. Nerland held the position of VP Finance of Wi-LAN Inc., a TSE publicly listed technology company.
				</p>
				<p>
					Nerland also held the position of President at RenoWorks, a public company on the TSX Venture Exchange where he remains a Director. He is also presently a Director of Corridor Interactive Technologies, a private software technology company. He also held the position of President and COO of Zi Corporation, an international, public software company selling Chinese language software technology. In this role, he oversaw worldwide software development operations, sales and marketing, and finance and administrative functions.
				</p>
				<p>
					Nerland received his Chartered Accountant designation while with KPMG and holds a Bachelor of Commerce degree from University of Calgary.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>7</ID>
			<Name>Vivian Farris</Name>
			<Title>SVP, Human Resources</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/viv_farris_headshot_120.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/viv_farris_headshot_50.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Vivian Farris, SVP, Human Resources, is a member of the Executive Team with global responsibility for recruiting, talent management, retention and employee programs worldwide. Farris is based in Calgary.
				</p>
				<p>
					Farris has more than 13 years of human resources experience for some of the leading visual content and design companies in the world. Prior to her role at Corbis, she was a founding partner of Veer and Vice President of Human Resources. Under Farris’ vision and leadership, Veer became known for its innovative human resources programs. In the company’s six short years, it was twice named one of the Top 100 companies in Canada, top 25 companies in Alberta and one of the top 10 companies in Calgary.
				</p>
				<p>
					Previously, she managed human resources strategy and operations for companies including Getty Images, EyeWire, Adobe Studios and Image Club Graphics, overseeing activities across North America and Europe.
				</p>
				<p>
					Vivian Farris is married with two young sons.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>8</ID>
			<Name>Don Wieshlow</Name>
			<Title>SVP, Products</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Don_Wieshlow_headshot_120.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Don_Wieshlow_headshot_sm.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>
					Don Wieshlow, SVP of Products, is a member of the Executive Team and has overall global responsibility for content acquisition and management at Corbis. Wieshlow is based in Calgary.
				</p>
				<p>
					Prior to his role at Corbis, he was a founding partner and Vice President of Products for Veer, where he was part of the management team that grew the start-up to a profitable multi-million dollar business – becoming the 4th largest company in the industry before its acquisition by Corbis. Wieshlow directed teams responsible for the sourcing and production of over a million quality online products and established highly successful house brands in the type and photography categories.
				</p>
				<p>
					Previously, Wieshlow set up and directed EyeWire Europe’s European marketing and sales headquarters. He successfully integrated the EyeWire European operation after its acquisition by Getty Images. He previously worked at Adobe, managing elements of the Adobe Image Library Photography, Illustration and Motion product brand launch and the e-commerce strategy for Adobeshop.com.
				</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
		<Leader>
			<ID>9</ID>
			<Name>Rajiv Jain</Name>
			<Title>SVP &amp; CTO</Title>
			<ImagePath>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Images_rajiv_jain120.jpg</ImagePath>
			<ImageTumb>/Corporate/xml/Leadership/Images/Images_rajiv_jain.jpg</ImageTumb>
			<Detail>
				<p>As SVP &amp; CTO, Rajiv Jain is responsible for overseeing all technology activities for Corbis and is a member of the Executive Team based in the company’s Seattle headquarters.</p>
				<p>Rajiv has more than 20 years of technology and business experience in general management and product management roles with broad expertise in e-commerce, system software and internet solutions including Web 2.0 technologies.</p>
				<p>Prior to joining Corbis, Rajiv was SVP &amp; CTO at American Greetings Interactive (AGI), where he was responsible for the strategic technological and digital development of all its interactive properties. While at AGI, he led the integration of two acquisitions in the photo-space, WebShots and PhotoWorks. Previously, Rajiv was General Manager for e-commerce at Cingular/AT&amp;T Wireless and held executive and senior management positions at Portal (now Oracle), IBM, Autodesk.</p>
				<p>Rajiv is a gold-medallist graduate from Indian Institute of Technology in Kanpur, India and holds Masters of Science from University of Rochester NY. He holds 10 software patents under his name.</p>
			</Detail>
		</Leader>
	</team>
</CorbisCorp>